Hm.
Good morning
Good morning.
Alice, can you sit down for a minute?
Yes, excuse me.
We're filming at the Sunshine Aquarium today, right?
Yes, I know.
Since we're here, I'd like to buy souvenirs for the three of us.
Can you go buy it for us?
I will.
Alice...
I hope that's okay.
I'll be fine.
There's a new item that I'm interested in, but I can't remember what it is.
Can you tell me? I forgot... a little bit.
But I could give you a hint if we do a little PR mission for the aquarium.
Can you do that for me? Okay. Well, I'll do my best for both of you.
I'll do my best. I'm going home this year. I'm going home.
Good night.
That's a train.
Clairis.
Mission accomplished.
Oh, I understand perfectly.
Blue.
Find it, Alice, the new one.
Okay, so here's the first mission.
I'll open it.
Nice to meet you.
There you go.
What?
English.
I can't read English.
You're gonna have to try harder.
Do you know what that means?
Takeout.
Oh!
Baby.
Gab Bear.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Can you see it?
There's only a baby in there, but I don't really care, because there's something in there, and that something is a baby.
I'm just saying, baby, that's all I'm buying here and there, okay?
A photo, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something, something...
It's the most important thing. It's kind of Japanese.
Maybe... I don't know. I'll answer here.
I don't know. I'll answer here.
Can you hang in there?
We can't go together.
It's like we have to stay here.
I know.
I'm gonna make a stop.
I'll call you.
Hang in there. Hang in there.
I'll do my best.
Yes, ma'am.
We've arrived at the aquarium.
I saw the mission earlier.
I kind of know what it's about, but...
I'm a little worried about whether it will be okay.
But I'll do my best for them.
Am I right?
Okay, I'll go look for it.
It's a beautiful day.
Where is it?
Oh! There's the penguins!
Can you see them?
They're so cute!
I saw them!
They say they're called Seppe penguins.
What was that?
The mission.
Client photo of a baby.
Come on!
You know, you kind of sound like a penguin.
Like a penguin.
What do you think?
He thinks he's a penguin.
Maybe we'll take a picture of him?
I don't know. What do you think?
I think he's gonna take a picture.
Yeah, a selfie.
He's cute.
Penguin photo. You want to take a photo with me?
I'll take a picture with you.
You want to take a selfie?
That's so cute.
Selfies are badass.
You want to take a picture?
Oh, my God.
Sushi bar... someone shook it.
How about this?
The mission is to see if you've succeeded, isn't it?
Alice, one more mission, right?
Is this penguin a baby?
It's a baby.
I think I got it.
Can you do it?
I'm in.
What, are we gonna take a picture together? Sort of.
No?
We got it.
Is it the right one?
Alice.
You should take a walk around the penguin area a little more.
You might want to.
Yay.
Well, let's go for a stroll.
No, I don't think that was a ground rumbling.
Baby, where are you?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, is that her?
Is that her?
He's so cute!
Cute!
Cute! It's a baby.
Baby cape penguin
Baby
All right, baby.
Isn't this one? It's a baby, baby.
Okay, let's try this one more time.
I found the baby.
Ta-da!
I took a picture.
What do you think?
All right.
Alice was right.
Wow!
Well done.
Alice, you speak English.
Oh, my God.
That's great!
Now I'd like to get a hint about the stage.
Alice's first key word is...
Penguin.
Yes!
I have no idea.
There's a lot of stuffed animals and stuff.
Then let's get another mission.
Yes, sir.
I got the next mission.
I'll take it.
English again!
And it's a long sentence.
Selfie.
The Sea Lions
Swimming in the Sunshine Aquaring
Sunshine Aquaring
Yes, sir.
You got it?
We don't even know what the Sea Lions are.
I'm sorry. I can't help you at all.
Aqua Ring isn't very good either.
Sunshine Aqualung.
I know, right?
But I have a feeling it's a famous place.
Good luck!
Aqua Ring.
Alice, do you know where the Sea Lions are?
No, no, no, no, no. Sea Lions. It's kind of like the ocean.
Alice, swimming? Yes!
Any animals on the sign that we can see in English?
Animals.
Something like a list of animals.
I don't know where the animal list is.
The penguins are over there.
Back towards the entrance of the road we just came from.
Maybe it's that way.
Maybe it's this way.
Where is it?
It's out there somewhere.
It's tiny.
Oh...
It doesn't look too good.
No?
Ah! Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
There's more.
But no.
No?
Aah! Aah! Aah! Aah!
There it is!
What? It's right there.
Sea lions, don't you mean sea lions?
Sea lions!
Sea lions.
We're going to the sea lion place.
Let's go.
I see.
I learned a new word.
Ring-ring-ring.
Not ring?
Not a ring?
Isn't that a ring?
Like, I just saw something go by back there.
That's awesome.
That's great.
Behind you.
Behind.
Oh, my God.
Top.
Am I right?
Yes, I'm sure.
If you've come this far with the selfies, this is the aquaring.
It's only a ring.
It looks like a ring.
Are you sure this is the same as the Sanshoan or the Aqua Ring?
It's right, Alice.
Is it right?
I'm just gonna take a selfie.
Selfies.
What's a selfie?
It's a little too early for that.
Okay, let's just take one picture.
Let's take a picture.
Yeah, it's there. It's in the right direction.
Yeah, it's in the right direction.
Uh, let's see.
Let's take it from outside the ring.
It seemed like it would be easier to see out there.
Oh, I got it. I got it.
Ah, ah, ah, I got it. I got it.
It's close.
No, but there's a photo I have to take.
This is a take-a-photo.
Yeah, it's the take-out selfie I was talking about.
What does that mean?
I was just with the penguins.
I was with the penguins.
I took a take-out selfie with the penguins.
Oh.
Oh?
Wow.
What's going on?
Wait a minute. You want me to go after him? I'll wait.
That's a lot of shots. That's a lot of shots. Give me the best one you got.
Ready?
Where is it?
Wait, it's not there.
I'm in the forelock.
I can't get the angle.
Just a little bit more.
I'll try taking it from a little further away. Oh, I think I can get it from here.
Oh, that's good. It's coming. It's coming.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming. It's coming.
He's looking at me, he's looking at me.
How's it going? How's it look? I got it. I got it!
Like this?
Stabic color.
Oh, good picture.
Too good picture.
Too many good pictures. Hey, Nae-chan, next time.
She's cute. So, the mission was a success.
You understood well, didn't you? Now, Gostelevi.
I see.
Yes, I did it once. It's a selfie. Wow! I see!
Thank you! I'm ready for the next mission.
What's the keyword?
Near Joy
The keyword is "near joy".
Pink for "near joy", you know? I wonder what it is.
So, the third mission.
The last mission.
Alice, bring us a souvenir.
I'll do my best. Until the end.
Okay, I'll open it. English again.
English again?
Take is a photo.
In front of...
Jellyfish.
Fish, fish, fish, fish, fish...
Yes, I think I'll go inside.
I haven't figured out what it is yet.
I don't know what it is yet, but I think it's a jellyfish.
It's mysterious, Jellyfish.
The name never changes.
Jellyfish.
Oh, my God.
What's Julie say?
Julie?
Julie.
Look at the sign.
I made a mistake.
I'll look for it.
Is it a fish?
There you go.
There's a beautiful Clari.
I usually like to look at Clary.
Look at the sign.
It's beautiful.
You know, if you take a picture, Fran.
Isn't it amazing when you take a picture?
Isn't it amazing? Look at that.
I'll see you soon.
Juli?
Wait, this could be bad.
It says "jellyfish" on it.
Jellyfish?
Yes, it does.
Jellyfish jellyfish.
That's amazing.
Is this supposed to be a picture?
Do you know who this is?
You're in the light.
I'm in the light.
It's nice, isn't it? Let's take it here, shall we?
Oh, my God.
It's blue.
Here we go.
It's lit up.
He's so cute.
I got a lot of pictures.
Did you get a lot of pictures?
It's funny.
So this was a successful mission.
You got the lamp.
You're a native too.
Thank you.
I'm glad we could do it all here.
That's great.
Oh, my God.
Okay, the key word is...
Strap.
Strap!
What was it before?
Remember the clue?
Do you remember?
The clue is...
Let's see...
Come on.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Back to square one?
One more time?
How many pictures did I take the first time?
The first one was a baby penguin.
That's why the clue was penguins earlier.
Penguin g-holder.
And?
What's that?
And from the feet.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Lim.
Keyword keyword, what happened to the second one, remember?
Remember the second one?
And now the third one?
The third one.
Keyholder.
Well, well, well.
Is it a strap?
Wrong strap.
I got a souvenir from the keyword "power supply near-joy strap".
Newly released!
Yes, new release.
I'll go look for it.
I'd be happy if you could find it for me.
Bring it to me, Alice.
I'll get it.
I'll wait for you.
I'm hungry.
Come here, come here.
I'll be right down.
Very single.
Cute on both hands.
In the garden.
Find it, Alice.
It's a strap, isn't it?
Cute.
I'm looking for a strap.
It's a strap. It's a new product.
It doesn't say "new" on it.
Oh, no.
No, it's not.
Penguin.
Here it comes.
Not this one.
I'm a little frustrated about the meaning of near-jewish.
But I think there's yellow in it.
But I don't know.
I don't know... other than yellow.
A crown.
It's got a crown on it.
A king.
Let's take a look at this one.
Oh, look at that.
Ah! Huh? Huh? Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look, I found one with a crown.
That's it, I know it!
That's the one!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Which one do I get?
Oh, there's different kinds?
Oh, are we matching?
Matching?
Well, Alice, you can each pick one.
Each one? Different kinds?
It doesn't matter.
Okay, okay.
Which one do you want, Alice?
Let's choose Alice.
Yeah, let's pick one. I'll keep it a secret.
Okay, well, I won't taste it, but I'll see you later. Okay, well, look forward to it.
I'll see you later.
Oh, my God!
I've been here since 2012.
I'm sorry, Gal, but I'll be fine.
I'm not judging people!
I'm sure it's great that you have such a strong relação squid Д trans
Good job on the top of the battle!
I'm so happy for you! Good, good, good, good!
Did you change it?
Yes, I did.
Oh! I changed it.
Then, open the package.
Movie of leaving
It's coming back as an adult.
Your breath is different.
His posture is different, too.
He didn't say anything about opening the package.
Oh, that one.
It's cute.
I put it in, though.
Here, I've got something for both of you.
I've got a little something for you guys, so here you go.
Look at how cute he is!
Thank you, Rickshaw!
Cute, cute, cute, cute...
Boo boo!
I mean, was it actually right?
What was the T-ARDS?
T-ARDS was penguins, near-joys, and straps.
Well, I don't know.
This is a se
You're right!
Thank you so much!
Adelie penguin on the go, acrylic key
I'll put it on a little keep it on the penguin you bought for me
I'll put it on a little keep it!
I really appreciate your hard work.
It was difficult... difficult... because I couldn't read English.
But I was calm. I was very attentive.
Running errands.
Thank you for your hard work. You were so mature. You did your best.
Thank you. So, if you thought Alice did a great job, please click the Good button and subscribe to our channel.
That's all for now, Nearly Called Joy!